justrentals.com 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy Statement | Justproperty.Com | JustProperty.com

Budget

-

  * AED 0 
  * AED 20,000 
  * AED 30,000 
  * AED 40,000 
  * AED 50,000 
  * AED 60,000 
  * AED 70,000 
  * AED 80,000 
  * AED 90,000 
  * AED 100,000 
  * AED 110,000 
  * AED 120,000 
  * AED 140,000 
  * AED 160,000 
  * AED 180,000 
  * AED 200,000 
  * AED 220,000 
  * AED 250,000 
  * AED 300,000 
  * AED 350,000 
  * AED 400,000 
  * AED 500,000 
  * AED 600,000 
  * AED 700,000 

  * AED 0 
  * AED 20,000 
  * AED 30,000 
  * AED 40,000 
  * AED 50,000 
  * AED 60,000 
  * AED 70,000 
  * AED 80,000 
  * AED 90,000 
  * AED 100,000 
  * AED 110,000 
  * AED 120,000 
  * AED 140,000 
  * AED 160,000 
  * AED 180,000 
  * AED 200,000 
  * AED 220,000 
  * AED 250,000 
  * AED 300,000 
  * AED 350,000 
  * AED 400,000 
  * AED 500,000 
  * AED 600,000 
  * AED 700,000 

Alert 

Map View 

List View 

Shortlist (0) 

Area

Min - Max

  * 0 sq. ft. 
  * 500 sq. ft. 
  * 600 sq. ft. 
  * 700 sq. ft. 
  * 800 sq. ft. 
  * 900 sq. ft. 
  * 1,000 sq. ft. 
  * 1,500 sq. ft. 
  * 2,000 sq. ft. 
  * 2,500 sq. ft. 
  * 3,000 sq. ft. 
  * 3,500 sq. ft. 
  * 4,000 sq. ft. 
  * 4,500 sq. ft. 
  * 5,000 sq. ft. 
  * 5,500 sq. ft. 
  * 6,000 sq. ft. 
  * 6,500 sq. ft. 
  * 7,000 sq. ft. 
  * 7,500 sq. ft. 
  * 8,000 sq. ft. 
  * 8,500 sq. ft. 
  * 9,000 sq. ft. 
  * 9,500 sq. ft. 
  * 10,000 sq. ft. 
  * 10,500 sq. ft. 
  * 11,000 sq. ft. 
  * 11,500 sq. ft. 
  * 12,000 sq. ft. 
  * 12,500 sq. ft. 
  * 13,000 sq. ft. 
  * 13,500 sq. ft. 
  * 14,000 sq. ft. 
  * 14,500 sq. ft. 
  * 15,000 sq. ft. 
  * 15,500 sq. ft. 
  * 16,000 sq. ft. 
  * 16,500 sq. ft. 
  * 17,000 sq. ft. 
  * 17,500 sq. ft. 
  * 18,000 sq. ft. 
  * 18,500 sq. ft. 
  * 19,000 sq. ft. 
  * 19,500 sq. ft. 
  * 20,000 sq. ft. 

  * 0 sq. ft. 
  * 500 sq. ft. 
  * 600 sq. ft. 
  * 700 sq. ft. 
  * 800 sq. ft. 
  * 900 sq. ft. 
  * 1,000 sq. ft. 
  * 1,500 sq. ft. 
  * 2,000 sq. ft. 
  * 2,500 sq. ft. 
  * 3,000 sq. ft. 
  * 3,500 sq. ft. 
  * 4,000 sq. ft. 
  * 4,500 sq. ft. 
  * 5,000 sq. ft. 
  * 5,500 sq. ft. 
  * 6,000 sq. ft. 
  * 6,500 sq. ft. 
  * 7,000 sq. ft. 
  * 7,500 sq. ft. 
  * 8,000 sq. ft. 
  * 8,500 sq. ft. 
  * 9,000 sq. ft. 
  * 9,500 sq. ft. 
  * 10,000 sq. ft. 
  * 10,500 sq. ft. 
  * 11,000 sq. ft. 
  * 11,500 sq. ft. 
  * 12,000 sq. ft. 
  * 12,500 sq. ft. 
  * 13,000 sq. ft. 
  * 13,500 sq. ft. 
  * 14,000 sq. ft. 
  * 14,500 sq. ft. 
  * 15,000 sq. ft. 
  * 15,500 sq. ft. 
  * 16,000 sq. ft. 
  * 16,500 sq. ft. 
  * 17,000 sq. ft. 
  * 17,500 sq. ft. 
  * 18,000 sq. ft. 
  * 18,500 sq. ft. 
  * 19,000 sq. ft. 
  * 19,500 sq. ft. 
  * 20,000 sq. ft. 

__Clear

__Advanced Search

**Last Updated 30 June 2019**

## **Privacy policy**

### **1\. INTRODUCTION**

    1. JRD Group DMCC (“JRD”), a company registered in Dubai, with a registered address at office Unit 2201, Mazaya Business Avenue AA1, Jumeirah Lakes Towers, Dubai, UAE, owns and operates the website justproperty.com (“Website” or “Justproperty”).  
    2. We may amend this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) at any time, and such amendments become effective from the date upon which we make them available on the Website. When we change this Policy in a material way, we will update the "last modified" date at the end of this Policy. 
    3. Throughout this Policy, the terms “we", "our", "us" means JRD and its subsidiaries, employees, officers, agents, affiliates or assigned parties.
    4. Justproperty is a service provider contracting with and delivering products to Clients (defined as those who are bound by the Client Terms and Conditions), as well as, the availability and use of the Website to Users (defined as those who are bound by the Terms of Use) (hereinafter “Service(s)”).  
    5. Propertyfinder FZ-LLC (“PF FZ-LLC) is the Data Controller in respect of personal data collected and processed through the Website. Data Controller means a person (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) or legal entity, who, determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.
    6. JRD is the Data Processor in respect of personal data collected and processed through the Website.  Data Processor means a person (either alone or jointly in common with other persons) or legal entity, who, deals with personal data as instructed by a controller for specific purposes and services offered to the controller that involve personal data processing.
    7. JRD is part of the Property Finder Group of companies, which shall for reference purposes also include JRD Group DMCC (doing business as PropSpace and JustProperty), PF FZ-LLC, Property Finder LLC (Qatar), PFB Bahrain S.P.C., Al Baheth Al Maloomati Co (Kingdom of Saudi Arabia doing business as eSimsar), Property Finder Lebanon SARL, Propertyfinder Morocco SARL (doing business as Sarouty), Propertyfinder Egypt LLC, and M.I.B.M.E Mortgage Broker Owned by Propertyfinder Arabia Singl Company LLC (doing business as Mortgage Finder).  These group of companies shall be referred to in this Policy, collectively, as the “Property Finder Group”, and, individually a “Property Finder Group Company”.

### **2**. ****YOUR INFORMATION****

    1. We collect the following types of information that identifies or is associated with you (" **Personal Information** "):
      1. **Contact information, communications and transaction information** : When you register on the Website as a user or otherwise, update your information, purchase any goods or services, take part in promotions or campaigns or contests, sign into our mobile application using your contact details, account details or a social media account, send emails to us, send support requests, contact estate agents via forms or phone numbers made available on our website, provide feedback, or when you report a problem with our website, you provide us with information that we store and process. Such information may include your name, address, phone number, email address, purchase and transaction history, billing information (including credit card information) and interests. 
    2. **Information about how you use the Website** : We also receive information from you as a result of your visits to, and use of, the Website. We automatically collect certain information to help us administer and protect the Services, analyze usage, and improve users’ experience. The information collected includes, amongst others:
      1. IP address and browser type
      2. Date and time you access a portion of the Website
      3. Device information including Unique Device Identifier (UDID), MAC address, Identifier For Advertisers (IFA), and similar identifiers we or others may assign
      4. Device operating system and other technical facts
      5. Pages visited and content viewed, stored, and purchased
      6. Information or text entered
      7. Links and buttons clicked
      8. URLs visited before and after you use our Services

 3.  **Payment Data** : Payment Data is the information that you provide when you make online purchases. This may include your payment instrument number (e.g., credit card), your name and billing address, and the security code associated with your payment instrument (e.g., the CSV or  CVV). The Payment Data, to the extent consisting of details related to the manner and mode of payment of fees for the use of the Website and Services (such as details of your bank account, credit card, debit card, net banking, etc.), submitted by you while making payment of fees: (a) goes through the safe and secure transaction process provided by PF FZ-LLC’s payment gateway partners; (b) goes through the Visa or Mastercard pages, as the case may be, based on your payment method(s) in order to prevent any misuse of your payment details; and (c) is not shared with the Website, any Property Finder Group Company, their subsidiaries, affiliates and third parties or any other users of the Website and Services.

4.  **Information We Receive from other Sources** : We may receive information about you if you use any of the websites that we, or any Property Finder Group Company, operate, or from any other services that we provide.  We are also working closely with third parties, including but not limited to, business partners, service providers, advertising networks, analytics providers, and search information providers.  We may receive information about you from such third parties. This information may be combined with other information you provide to us, as described above.

5.The table at  **Annex 1**  sets out further information about the categories of Personal Information that we collect about you. 

###   **3.**   ** **COLLECTING AND USING INFORMATION****

    1. Most of this Website can be used without giving us any information. We will indicate to you where the provision of certain personal information is required in order for us to provide you certain features of the Website or certain services. If you choose not to provide such Personal Information, we may not be able to provide the Website or our services to you or to respond to your other requests. 
    2. Certain third-party technology may also involve collection and usage of information from you, including but not limited to, Google Analytics (a description of their specific data collection and processing practices can be found via the following link: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Please see below how you can opt out of the collection of your personal information in this way. 
    3. We use Personal Information to provide you with the following purposes:
      1. To provide any services that you request from us or another Property Finder Group Company;
      2. To provide a better service, and in particular to: keep internal records, as well as, improve our products, services and the Website;
      3. To communicate with you if you have ordered, purchased or participated in anything on the Website;
      4. To contact you for market research purposes;
      5. To provide you with information about new opportunities, promotions, special offers and other information that we may feel is relevant to you. If you contact us via the Website, or via email to the contacts set out on the Website, we may keep a record of that correspondence;
      6. To provide you, or permit other Property Finder Group Company, or selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services that may interest you;
      7. To customize or enhance your experience on our website and services, including via the display of adverts and direct communications you receive from us, which may be based on your activity on our website or the website of any other Property Finder Group Company;
      8. To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you, which may be based on your activity on our website, or the website of another Property Finder Group Company or third parties’ website(s); and
      9. To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our website about goods or services that may interest you or them, which may be based on your activity on our website, or the website of another Property Finder Group Company or third parties’ website(s).
    4. We use Personal Information we collect about you automatically to help us make the Website more useful to customers (including to help us assess content of interest to visitors), and for other purposes such as determining the Website’s technical design specifications and identifying system performance or problem areas, for tracking activity on the Website, preparing reports, assessing trends, and otherwise monitoring the way in which the Website is being used none of which would be in a way that personally identifies any users. 
    5. The table at  **Annex 1**  sets out further information about how we use the Personal Information we collect from you, and the legal basis we rely on to process the Personal Information in this way.

### **4.**   ** **DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION****

    1. We may share your Personal Information in connection with the purposes above with any Property Finder Group Company.
    2. We may share your Personal Information with third parties in the following circumstances:
      1. selected real estate brokers, real estate brokerage firms, agents, developers or other service providers that we use, where you have asked us to do so or it is an implicitly inherent part of your use of the Website. For example, when you enquire about a property of interest to you, we will pass your Personal Information to the estate agents handling that property sale or rental. Upon receipt of your Personal Information, the relevant third party is the Data Controller and their use of your information will be governed by their own terms of use and privacy policy; 
      2. business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors which we may use in connection with the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you; and
      3. we partner with and are supported by service providers around the world. Personal Information will be made available to these parties only when necessary to fulfill the services they provide to us, such as software, system, and platform support; direct marketing services; cloud hosting services; advertising; data analytics; and order fulfillment and delivery. Our third-party service providers are not permitted to share or use Personal Information we make available to them for any other purpose than to provide services to us.
    3. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties:
      1. in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your Personal Information to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets, along with its professional advisers. If PF FZ LLC, a Property Finder Group Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, Personal Information held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
      2. if required in order to obtain professional advice; 
      3. if we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or
      4. to protect the rights, property, or safety of PF FZ LLC, JRD, other Property Finder Group Companies, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection.
    4. The table at Annex 1 sets out further information about the recipients of your Personal Information. 

### ****5\. SECURITY****

    1. Keeping your Personal Information secure and preventing unauthorized access is of utmost priority to us, and we take all steps reasonably necessary to protect your Personal Information against any unauthorised access, use, alteration, disclosure or destruction. Whilst we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to secure and safeguard your Personal Information, due to the nature of the internet and available technology, we cannot guarantee that the Personal Information provided by you or that is transmitted via this Website or by e-mail is totally secure and safe.

### ****6\. STORAGE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
****

    1. The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in a country outside the country in which the Property Finder Group Company is located, whose website you have accessed in order for the information to be collected.  It may also be processed by staff operating outside such country, who work for us or for one of our suppliers. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated in accordance with this Policy.
    2. Where we have given you, or where you have created a password which is part of our services or allows you to access parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.  We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

### ****7\. YOUR RIGHT TO ACCESS AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION  
****

    1. We respect your right to access and control your information, and we will respond to requests for information and, where applicable, will correct, amend, or delete your Personal Information.  Any such request can be made to privacy@propertyfinder.ae.
    2. **Access to personal information:**  If you request access to your Personal Information, we will gladly , subject to any relevant legal requirements and exemptions, including identity verification procedures, provide you with (i) confirmation of whether, and where, we are processing your Personal Information; (ii) information about the categories of Personal Information we are processing, the purposes for which we process that Personal Information and information about how we determine applicable retention periods; (iii) information about the categories of recipients with whom we may share your Personal Information; and (iv) a copy of the Personal Information we hold about you. Before providing data to you, we may ask for proof of identity and sufficient information about your interaction with us so that we can locate any relevant data. We will not charge you a fee for providing you with a copy of your data (unless we are allowed to do so by law).
    3. **Correction:**  You have the right to correct or amend your Personal Information if it is inaccurate or requires updating. 
    4. **Deletion.  **You have the right, in certain circumstances, to request deletion of your Personal Information if the continued processing of that Personal Information is not justified; however, this is not always possible due to legal requirements and other obligations and factors.
    5. **Restriction**. You have the right, in some circumstances, to require us to limit the purposes for which we process your Personal Information if the continued processing of the Personal Information in this way is not justified, such as where the accuracy of the Personal Information is contested by you.
    6. **Portability**. You have the right, in certain circumstances, to receive a copy of the Personal Information you have provided to us in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format that supports re-use, or to request the transfer of your Personal Information to another person.
    7. **Objection**. You have the right to object to any processing based on our legitimate interests and you have grounds for making such an objection in light of your particular situation. There may be compelling reasons for us to continue to process your Personal Information, and we will assess and inform you if that is the case. You can object to marketing activities for any reason. 
    8. **Marketing preferences:**  [We will only send you marketing messages if you have given us your consent to do so]. To opt out of email marketing, you can use the unsubscribe link found in the email communication you receive from us or by sending an email to privacy@proeprtyfinder.ae. For other marketing preferences, you can contact us via any relevant link in the marketing communication, or by sending an email to privacy@proeprtyfinder.ae. Information related to controlling cookies, and information related to Interest-Based and Mobile Advertising can be found in this Policy.

### ****8\. USE OF COOKIES****

    1. Like many websites, this Website uses cookies (which may also be placed and read by third party providers, including but not limited to Google Analytics and Double Click for Publisher.  Further information regarding Google partner sites can be found at the following link: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/), which are files that collect data and store information on your hard drive. Cookies are used for purposes that include but are not limited to allowing the user of such information or the website to identify account holders, track new users, record session information, and generally to optimize your experience.  For online advertising campaigns, cookies are automatically deleted after a period of time.
    2. Most browsers accept cookies automatically but if you choose you can disable the cookies from your browser (with the exception of some enhancements made to Google Analytics Advertising Features.  More information on such can be found here: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3450482?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/3450482?hl=en)), you may find that certain functions and features will not work as intended on the Services. The relevant settings will typically be found in the "options" or "preferences" menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful; otherwise you should use the "Help" option in your browser for more details:
      1. [Cookie settings in Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/products/windows)
      2. [Cookie settings in Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies)
      3. [Cookie settings in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)
      4. [Cookie settings in Safari web](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042?locale=en_GB) and [iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265).
    3. Deleting or blocking cookies may not be effective for all types of tracking technologies, such as Local Storage Objects (LSOs) like HTML5.
    4. We understand that you may want to know more about cookies. Here are some useful resources that provide detailed information about types of cookies, how they are used, and how you can manage your cookie preferences: [http://www.aboutcookies.org/](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### ****9\. USE OF THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS AND TRACKING PIXELS  
****

    1. This Website uses third party analytics providers, such as Google Analytics (“Third Party Analytics”). Third Party Analytics use cookies and/or text files to analyze website traffic. Information generated by cookies with your details (including your IP address) is transferred to servers operated by Third Party Analytics. Third Party Analytics process this information to evaluate your use of this Website, compile reports about this Website’s activity on our behalf, and deliver other related services regarding website and Internet use. Third Party Analytics may also share this information with third parties insofar as this is necessary or if these third parties process the information on behalf of them.
    2. In most cases (except as outlined in Clause 8.3) you may disable the cookies from your browser by adjusting your browser settings. However, in this scenario, you may not be able to make full use of all the functions available on this Website. 
    3. Third party tracking pixels are used on our Website. This means that third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from our Website and elsewhere on the internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target adverts. 

### ****10\. THIRD PARTY ADVERTISERS  
****

    1. We allow third party advertising networks to serve advertisements on our behalf.
    2. Third party advertisers may place cookies on the browsers of visitors to its website(s) and may send its own cookies to the visitors’ cookie file. The cookies will allow these third-party advertisers to apply their personalized retargeting technology and to serve personalized banners; third party advertisers may collect and use this data in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations (including but not limited to laws governing privacy, and data protection). 
    3. Third party advertisers will have their own Privacy Policy’s and these will be available on their websites. For further information on what third party advertisers we use for our Website please contact: privacy@propertyfinder.ae.

### ****11\. INTERNET-BASED ADVERTISING(IBA)  
****

    1. Interest-based advertising (IBA) allows us to deliver targeted advertising to users of our Services. IBA works by showing you advertisements that are based on the type of content you access or read. For example, as you browse our Services, one of the cookies placed on your device will be an advertising cookie so we can better understand what sort of pages or content you are interested in. The information collected about your device enables us to group you with other devices that have shown similar interests. We can then display advertising to categories of users that is based on common interests.
    2. If you want to opt out of receiving interest-based advertising, it does not mean that you will no longer receive advertising when you are using our Services. It just means that we will not use information collected about you for IBA and that any advertising you see will not be customized or relevant to you. You can exercise your online advertising choices at [http://optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/) or by clicking the AdChoices icon in an ad and following the instructions. You may also opt out of receiving interest-based ads from many sites through the Network Advertising Initiative's (NAI) Opt Out Tool ([http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices)) and in the EU at [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). Remember, if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you may need to opt out again.
    3. Mobile devices have an identifier that gives companies the ability to serve targeted ads to a specific mobile device. In many cases, you can turn off mobile device ad tracking or you can reset the advertising identifier at any time within your mobile device privacy settings. Another tool you can use to control advertising on your mobile device is the AppChoices App: [http://youradchoices.com/appchoices](http://youradchoices.com/appchoices). You may also choose to turn off location tracking on your mobile device. If you turn off ad tracking or location tracking, we will no longer use information collected from your device’s advertising identifier for the purposes of advertising. You may still see the same number of ads but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests.

### ****12\. LINKS AND CONNECTIONS TO AND USE OF OTHER THIRD-PARTY SERVICES  
****

    1. Our [Services may contain links to and may be used by you in conjunction with third-party apps, services, tools, and websites that are not affiliated with, controlled, or managed by us. Examples include but are not limited to Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter® and, third-party apps like voice software and readers. The privacy practices of these third parties will be governed by the parties’ own Privacy Statements. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by these third parties. You should review the privacy statements or policies applicable to these third-party services.
    2. Information that you provide to third-party companies is not covered by this Policy. 

### ****13\. PRIVACY OF MINORS  
****

    1. Our Services are not aimed at individuals under the age of eighteen years old (“minors”). If, however, we collect and use information about any minor, we will comply with the applicable laws.
    2. We hereby prohibit all minors from the use of any website or service governed by this Policy, which includes those websites and services operated or provided by the Property Finder Group of companies. 
    3. If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, then please contact us at privacy@propertyfinder.ae so that we can take steps to remove such information. 

### ****14\. CONTACT****

>   1. Please contact us at privacy@propertyfinder.ae if you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this Policy. 
>   2. If we are unable to deal with any issues you raise with us, you may also have the right to lodge a complaint to your national data protection authority.
> 

### **ANNEX – PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

**Category of personal information**

| 

**How we use it**

| 

**Legal basis for the processing**

| 

**Recipients**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
**Contact information  **such as your name, phone number and e-mail address.

| 

We may use this information to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service.

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract.

| 

We will share your personal information with the following:

**1\. Advertisers**. When you submit this information to enquire about a property or in response to a third party advertisement on the Website, we will submit these details to the relevant third party who is responsible for the content of the advertisement.   
 **2\. Campaign Monitor Pty Ltd.**   **(t/as "Campaign Monitor")** , our e-marketing platform, so that we can send marketing communications in accordance with your preferences.  
 **3\. Sendgrid, Inc.,  **our automated transactional e-mail platform provider, for the purpose of sending you service related communications.  
 **4\. Twilio, Inc.,  **our automated SMS platform provider, for the purpose of sending SMS messages to an Advertiser when information is submitted in relation to an advertised property.  
 **5\. Tableau Software, Inc** , our data analysis platform to assist us with analysing and improving our Service.  
 **6\. Moveable, Inc.** ,our service provider of e-marketing communication enhancement.  
  
We may share this information with licensed real estate brokers, developers and hoteliers (collectively, " **Advertisers** ") that advertise properties for sale or rent through our Website and our apps.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely providing a lead generation service to Advertisers.  
  
We may use this information to communicate with you, including sending service-related communications (such as responding to your enquiries).

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract.  
  
We may use this information to deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Service.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service, and for communicating with you effectively to respond to your queries or complaints.   
  
We may use this information to send you unsolicited marketing emails in accordance with your preferences.

| 

We will process your personal information for this purpose to the extent that you have given us consent to do so.  
  
We may use this information to send you unsolicited marketing communications in accordance with your preferences.

| 

We will process your personal information for this purpose to the extent that you have given us consent to do so.  
  
**Correspondence, comments and opinions.**  When you contact us directly, e.g. by email, phone or when you complete an online form, we will record your comments and opinions.

| 

We may use this information to address your questions, issues and concerns.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely communicating with users and responding to queries, complaints and concerns. 

| 

We will share your personal information with:

**1\. Campaign Monitor Pty Ltd.**   **(t/as "Campaign Monitor")** ,, our e-marketing platform, so that we can send you push notifications and marketing communications in accordance with your preferences.  
  
We may use this information to develop our marketing materials and to reward Advertisers.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely marketing.  
  
We may use this information to develop new products and features available through our Service or otherwise improve our Service.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely developing and improving our Service.  
  
We may use this information to determine products and services that may be of interest to you.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely marketing.   
  
We may use this information to send you solicited marketing communications and other information in response to your enquiries.

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract and to take steps prior to entering into a contract.  
  
We may use this information to send you unsolicited marketing communications in accordance with your marketing preferences.

| 

We will process your personal information for this purpose to the extent that you have given us consent to do so.  
  
**Legal representative details** , such as name, firm, address, telephone number and e-mail address.

| 

We may use this information to facilitate transactions with Advertisers.

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract or to take steps prior to entering into a contract.

| 

We may share this information with Advertisers for the purpose of facilitating transactions through our Service.   
  
**Content of telephone calls**. When you call us or an Advertiser, we may record your telephone calls. 

| 

We may use this information for call monitoring and training. 

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely reviewing the quality of our customer service (and that of our Advertisers) and staff training.

|    
  
We may use this information for to research and develop our products and services.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely developing and improving our products and services.  
  
We may use this information to inform our direct marketing. 

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely informing our direct marketing.  
  
**Preferences and prospective transaction details** , such as city and location of interest, preferred time and date to be contacted, purchase or rental budget, desired number of bedrooms, motivation for move, country/nationality, keywords.

| 

We may use this information to generate leads for Advertisers that use our Service to market real estate.

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract.

| 

When you submit this information in connection with an enquiry about a property, we will submit these details to the relevant Advertiser. 

We may also share this information with  **Diennea S.r.l. (t/as "MagNews")** , an e-marketing platform, in order to send targeted email marketing.   
  
We may use this information to provide customer support.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely administering the Service and providing customer support.   
  
We may use this information to inform our advertising, marketing, and research.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely marketing.  
  
**Information received from third parties, such as social networks.  **If you interact with our Service through a social network, we may receive information from the social network such as your name, profile information, and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties. The data we receive is dependent on your privacy settings with the social network.

| 

We may use this information to facilitate your access to the Service and the creation of your account on the Service.

| 

The processing is necessary for the performance of a contract, or to take steps prior to entering into a contract.

| 

We may share this information with Advertisers   
  
We may use this information to determine products and services that may be of interest to you.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely informing our direct marketing.  
  
**Account Preferences**. Preferences set for notifications, marketing communications, how our website is displayed and how you use the Service.

| 

We use this information to provide notifications, send marketing communications and display our Service in accordance with your choices.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interest, namely ensuring the user receives the correct marketing and other communications.

|    
  
**Location information**. Other than information you choose to provide to us, we do not collect information about your precise location. However, your device’s IP address may help us determine an approximate location.

| 

We use information you provide to us about your location to inform and plan our marketing strategy, as well as research and development for product innovation.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interest, namely informing our direct marketing strategy. 

|    
  
**All personal information set out above.**

| 

We will use all the personal information we collect to operate, maintain and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, to communicate with you, to monitor and improve our Service and business, and to help us develop new products and services.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to administer and improve the Service.

|    
  
**Information about how you access and use the Service.  **For example, the website from which you came and the website to which you are going when you leave our website, how frequently you access the Service, the time you access our Service and how long you use it for, the approximate location that you access the Service from, whether you access the Service from multiple devices, and other actions you take on the Service.

| 

We may use information about how you use and connect to our Service to present our Service to you on your device.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to tailor our Service to the user.

| 

We will share your personal information with the following:

**1.International Business Machines Corporation (t/as "Watson Marketing")** , our e-marketing platform, in connection with sending you unsolicited marketing communications in accordance with your preferences.  
Artificial Intelligence Techniques (t/as "artelnics"), a data analytics platform that helps us analyse user behaviour on our website.  
 **2\. Google LLC** , trading as "Google Analytics", a data analytics platform that helps us analyse user behaviour on our website.   
 **3.**   **Crazy Egg, Inc.** , a platform that helps us analyse user behaviour on our website.

**4\. Optimizely, Inc.** , a platform that helps us analyse user behaviour on our website for purpose of AB testing.

**5\. Snowplow Analytics Limited** , a data analytics platform that helps us analyse user behaviour on our website.   
 **6\. MaxMind, Inc** , a fraud detection service.   
 **7\. Moveable, Inc.** , our service provider of e-marketing communication enhancement.  
  
We may use this information to determine products and services that may be of interest to you for marketing purposes.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to inform our direct marketing.   
  
We may use this information to monitor and improve our Service and business, resolve issues and to inform the development of new products and services.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to monitor and resolve issues with our Service and to improve our Service generally.  
  
We may use this information to monitor our website use to detect fraud. 

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to detect and prevent fraud.   
  
**Log files and information about your device.**  We also collect information about the computer, tablet, smartphone or other electronic device you use to connect to our Service. This information can include details about the type of device, unique device identifying numbers, operating systems, browsers and applications connected to our Service through the device, and your IP address.

| 

We use information about how you use and connect to our Service to present our Service to you on your device.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to tailor our Service to the user.  
  
We use this information to determine products and services that may be of interest to you for marketing purposes.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to inform our direct marketing.   
  
We may use this information to monitor our website use to detect fraud. 

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to detect and prevent fraud.   
  
We use this information to monitor and improve our Service and business, resolve issues and to inform the development of new products and services.

| 

The processing is necessary for our legitimate interests, namely to monitor and resolve issues with our Service and to improve our Service generally.
